[Unsoiled Starlight]
[Episode 9]
[Adapted from Migu's novel
"Unsoiled Starlight"]
[Original Writer: Shan Gu Jun]
Lanlan.
Don't you recognize me?
Mr. Xu.
Why don't we
sit down to talk?
Okay.
Lanlan.
You really forgot.
When you were little...
when you were little like this,
your dad brought you to the company.
I even held you in my arms.
You didn't even know.
Why are you sitting so far away?
Sit here.
No, thanks.
I'm fine sitting here.
Still so stubborn.
But you...
you've really changed.
You're getting prettier and prettier.
I heard from the factory manager
that you were looking for me.
I've heard about
what's going on at the factory.
As for Qining,
I have some pull there.
Lanlan,
if you need my help,
I will
definitely spare no effort to help you.
How is it?
What are you doing?
Give it to me!
I never thought
that Shu Minghai's daughter
would come begging to me one day.
Seeing you up close like this,
I have to say
you're just as beautiful as your mother.
Fight back again,
and I'll strangle you!
Go ahead! I dare you!
I dare you!
I...
Who is it?
Enough.
Enough!
Stop fighting!
Don't make things worse.
For this kind of person,
it's not worth it.
It's okay now.
Call the police!
Come, tell me what happened.
What else is there to say?
Officer,
look at my injuries. They're so severe.
He almost crippled me!
I want to sue him!
Don't worry.
We will investigate thoroughly.
You better investigate properly!
Officer,
Xu Tao attempted to rape me.
We were just acting in self-defense.
Don't talk nonsense!
Did you take your pants off?
Wh-When did I ever rape you?
Wh-What are you doing?
I want to request an injury assessment.
Th-this...
It's not that serious.
She did it to herself.
- Stop arguing.
- Zhang.
Take him over there to make a statement.
Okay.
Come with me.
You just wait!
I'll make you pay for this!
Can I make a phone call first?
Mr. Zhuo.
I'm sorry.
Is your hand okay?
Lanlan.
No.
What I mean is...
I mean
just treat me like a fart
and let me go.
That's it.
That's what I mean.
Also,
Officer,
I want to
withdraw the police report.
Withdraw it.
I hurt myself.
I did it to myself.
Officer,
can we leave first?
Yes.
Why did you suddenly show up?
Of course I was worried about you.
If I hadn't asked
the factory secretary where you went...
Otherwise, I really can't imagine
what would have happened.
Thank you.
By the way,
is your hand
okay?
It's fine.
Can you take me to the airport later?
I have a flight
back to Senzhou tonight.
Shu Tinglan,
at a time like this,
can you stop thinking about
working overtime?
We both happen to be in Qining right now.
Since my hand is injured,
do you want to stay with me
for a couple of days?
Okay.
Hello.
Whatever you do,
I can turn a blind eye to it.
But you shouldn't abuse your connections
back home.
Okay.
Whether you did anything wrong or not,
you're asking for a favor
using someone else's connections.
Do you know how much
gossip
it will cause for them and yourself?
It won't happen again.
Did I cause trouble for you?
No.
Tomorrow,
I'll take you out.
Okay.
I just remembered that
Zhuoyuan Tech's new product launch
is next Monday.
How are you still in the mood
to wander around?
I'll wait for you in the crowd
An injured person needs an excuse to rest.
We're in sync. Unbelievable.
For the new product launch,
remember to come
and check it out if you have time.
Okay.
♪ It's the cloak of a close embrace ♪
♪ It's the steadfast days and
nights we share ♪
Wait for me here.
♪ When we weather the storm together,
don't forget ♪
♪ Breathing in the long river of time ♪
♪ My only promise is to you ♪
Where did you get a bike?
Get on.
♪ Between us ♪
♪ Suspicion feels so far away ♪
♪ When our eyes meet,
I feel your burning gaze ♪
♪ The wind by the shore has stilled ♪
♪ And you're smiling too ♪
♪ Make a wish to the wind ♪
♪ It's Cupid's arrow,
set loose from the string ♪
We'll be late if we don't ride faster,
kiddo.
Uncle.
What's the rush?
Why are you riding so fast?
Uncle?
Call me brother.
♪ Waiting for you in the crowd ♪
♪ Hearts in sync—how incredible ♪
♪ It's the familiar breath we share ♪
I just made an appointment
with the teacher.
♪ It's being each other's exception ♪
Let's go back to school together
and take a look.
They won't keep us out
for being late, will they?
If they do, I guess we'll have to stand there
and wait for a teacher to come get us.
♪ When tides ebb and flow, I look to you ♪
♪ Drowning in the long river of time ♪
[Qining City High School]
[Qining High School]
♪ You're the only air I breathe ♪
♪ Between us ♪
♪ The image of us holding each other ♪
♪ I see the dream encounter of that day ♪
Remember this was our class.
A bit further ahead was your class.
And right around the corner
was the math classroom.
How is your memory so good?
I can't remember clearly.
Shu Tinglan.
Yeah?
I remember everything
about you.
Do you remember
that one time you were
at the classroom door,
holding a workbook and calling me?
What did you call me?
Excuse me, is Zhuo Yuan here?
Zhuo Yuan?
Is Zhuo Yuan here?
Hey,
I'm right here.
Zhuo Yuan.
I found your workbook.
Read after me.
My name is Zhuo Yu'an.
[Zhuo Yu'an]
I don't remember.
Heartless.
Come on, pass it to me.
- Come on.
After all these years,
the school hasn't changed much.
It really hasn't changed much.
Come on, pass it to me.
I didn't expect
this noodle shop is still here.
I used to come here every day back then.
I would sit right there.
I know.
Because I sat right there.